<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Hugo Udemy Course</title>
    <link>http://example.org/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Hugo Udemy Course</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 21:39:39 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 21:39:39 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/resources/</guid>
      <description>As a wrap-up, the course talked about these resources
 Hugo documentation Hugo forums GitHub repo  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Next Steps</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/next-steps/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 21:34:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/next-steps/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;d like to upload this to GitHub using the tutorial at the end that explains how to do this using the command line. This is especially useful given I&amp;rsquo;m no longer using GitHub for Mac.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overall Thoughts</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/overall-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 21:11:34 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/overall-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>The course was a nice way to refresh my Hugo knowledge and round it out. The course did not delve into some of the more niche issues I&amp;rsquo;m figuring out on my own, but I didn&amp;rsquo;t expect that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Downloading Themes</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/downloading-themes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 20:24:35 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/downloading-themes/</guid>
      <description>The course went over downloading themes from the command line. Some of themes are no longer around as this is an older course.
The instructor pointed out that taking a look at themes to figure things out was a good point; this is something I do often.
Putting archetypes, css, or layouts can be added to your file and the theme will be overridden.
hugo new theme (theme name) is the command to enter if you&amp;rsquo;d like to create your own theme.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Topics Relevant to Work</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/relevant-topics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 20:15:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/relevant-topics/</guid>
      <description>Here are some of the topics that are relevant to work
 Partial templates Using where and ranging over things Shortcodes, both named and unnamed Adding disqus is an easy way to add comments Scheduled posts allow us to do just that. I could see this being useful for people.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reviewing the Basics</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/renewing-basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 20:14:58 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/renewing-basics/</guid>
      <description>The course was similar to the Youtube videos put out by Mike Dane in many ways. However, having worked with Hugo a bit so far, it was nice to have a refresher. For example, it was nice to use hugo new site quickstart and start from scratch once again.
I had largely forgotten about
 Downloading Themes posts with draft: true in frontmatter won&amp;rsquo;t render unless you specify Using the terminal to create new posts Archetypes being used to prefill frontmatter Taxonomies and how you customize them  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Other Topics discussed</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/other-topics-discussed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 19:35:53 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/other-topics-discussed/</guid>
      <description>3 ways to host your new site were discussed
 Uploading site to server Dropbox GitHub Pages (I am most familiar with this)  We also discussed migrating WordPress themes to Hugo.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>